First off, congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> And we're so happy to have you here in
the Carolinas.
>> Thank you.
>> All right, we're gonna kick things off
with Cassidy Hill.
>> Hey, Chris. Congratulations.
>> Hey, how you doing? Thank you.
>> Doing good. I have to ask, we saw a
picture from back, I think it was in
2021, and you were wearing a Carolina
Panthers jacket. What? Like, why? How
did you find yourself in that jacket
back in 2021?
>> I've been a fan. I'm I'm a long time
Panther fan. Man, I've been a Panther
fan since
third grade. So, just a dream come true.
>> What led you to becoming a Panthers fan
in the third grade?
>> So, I play for a team called the
Greenwood Panthers. Uh, I wore a jersey
that had Panthers on it back in the day.
Cam Newton was quarterback. Uh, y had
Luke Keat Lee, y'all had Stephen Smith,
Steve Smith, y'all going Josh Norman,
y'all was going to Super Bowl. I played
quarterback at the time. Cam New, they
my favorite players of all time. So, I
just I kind of just roll with it. Blue
is my favorite color. So, I literally
just roll with the Panthers and I never
look back.
>> I mean, like you said, kind of because
of that, this is a dream come true. Did
you imagine that this is where the night
was going for you?
>> Uh, no, I did not. Uh, I I ain't know
what was going to happen to be honest,
but I'm glad this happened.
>> Well, congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> We'll go with Sheena Quick.
>> Hi, Chris. Congratulations. I'm Sheena
Qu. Welcome to Carolina.
>> And I kind of kind of wanted to
piggyback on what Cassidy asked you. Um,
can you just kind of walk us through
what this process has been like for you
all the way up until getting that phone
call from the Panthers?
>> Uh, the draft has been stressful. I
ain't going to lie to you. Draft was
crazy. I've been anxious. I was nervous.
I didn't think I was going to get
drafted the third round. So, for my
favorite team to call me and select me
is like just takes everything away.
Thank you,
>> Basher.
>> Hi, Chris. Bashtart with Carolina Blitz.
Congratulations again. Uh, you did your
30 visit here in uh you did a 30 visit
here. Just tell us about that. The
interaction with Dave and Dan and the
vibes you got while you were here in
Charlotte.
>> Uh, I mean, one, like I said, thousand
times my favorite team. So, this visit
was the visit I was looking forward to
the most. I got there, met the receiver
coach, great guy. Met the GM, great guy.
Met the OC, great guy. Met the head
coach, great guy. So, Bob was amazing.
Uh, I feel like my 30 visit paid off for
them selecting me. So,
>> you're going to be playing with Bryce
Young. Uh, what are your thoughts on
him?
>> Uh, I mean, I went to Tennessee, so he
went to Bama, so uh, no shade, but I
remember watching Bryce Young when in
2022 when Tennessee beat Brass Young.
Brass Young was balling though. Brush
Young will balling. He's probably the
most underrated quarterback in the
league and I didn't want to take some
stress off his shoulder to be honest.
>> Thank you,
>> Scott. Balor.
>> Uh, yes. Congratulations to you. Um, we
understand you're super fast. I wonder
if you could describe your speed to us.
>> Uh, I wouldn't say super fast, but I
mean I'm pretty fast. Uh, yeah, I ran
437. Uh, I kind of fall started. So, I
really could have ran like a 434 or a
little slower or a little faster than
that. So, y'all going to see my speed
for sure. I'll leave it like that.
>> Tell us a little bit more too about your
playing style in general. How would you
describe it?
>> Uh, I'm a deep threat. Uh, I love manto
man coverage. Uh, I'm a playmaker. You
get to throw the ball my way. I'mma go
get it. Uh, and that's me. I'm a
playmaker. I'm a guy you can count on
third and three, third and eight, third
and 20. I feel like I'm a guy who's a
gonna make a play. So, uh, last thing
for me, but Monroe Freeling is from
Georgia, and I know that Georgia and
Tennessee have a little rivalry. He's
their first round pick here. Offensive
tackle. You going to get along with him?
Okay.
>> Uh, what school you went to?
>> Georgia.
>> Uh, yeah, we should get along good. Uh,
they beat us a couple times, but I had a
great game, so I'm sure mutual respect
between us.
>> Thanks,
>> Joe Pson, followed by Jeff Hawkins.
Chris, congrats, man.
>> Thank you. Thank you.
>> Hey, um, wanted Canales had an
interesting breakdown of you. He said
you are one of the few deep ball guys
that lands on your feet and you have
really good balance and come down with
those, not just with the ball, but on
your feet. How are you able to do that,
>> man? I'm just I don't I don't know. Just
God uh given ability. Uh when the ball's
in the air, I go, I don't really think
when the ball's in the air, I just my
body reacts to it and I feel like my
body just allows me to land on my feet.
So, it's just natural to me to be
honest.
>> And did I hear you say you had a little
bit of a false start or it would have
been like a 434?
>> Yeah, I would have been uh Yeah, I moved
uh you know the combine, the laser, they
get you off any movement. So, I move
slightly and before I even get to
running, it's like point4 seconds
already before I get to moving. So, it
would been a fast 40. I was trying to go
again, but uh had a few phone calls with
some guys. They recommended me not to go
again, but I was trying to get my 40
down from a 437 to a 434 or 433.
Then also uh obviously they took a
receiver the last couple years. Last
year, uh McMillan rookie of the year.
What do you think about joining this
room and what do you bring that maybe
they don't have uh currently?
>> Uh he's been a dog for Arizona. Uh he's
he's been a playmix Arizona. Uh he won
off the player of the year uh rookie
this year. So uh I'm most respected him.
He's a dog. Uh I plan on learning from
him and hopefully he teach me some
things. Uh I hope I just add uh the deep
ball out there. Hope they add a
playmaker. Uh not even just deep ball
out there. Uh I I feel like I can do
anything. So hopefully him on one side,
me on the other side, we can just make
things work and be unstoppable.
>> Thanks.
>> No problem.
Hey, greetings. Um, and congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> I Hey, I just wanted to follow up on
your uh your Cam Newton fandom. Um,
>> what what was the one play that you
remember that that made you a fan and
and what and what did you learn from
watching him play?
>> Uh, I I wouldn't say one play. I say one
I knew him was a good teammate. Uh, for
sure. You saw him giving the ball to the
kids uh every game. Great guy. Uh,
shoot. just a celebration, just him
getting dabbing, whipping, hitting the
Superman, just him being a a fun guy to
watch. It made me fall in love with him.
>> Um, have you adopted any kind of
celebration yourself or or anything to
>> to pay homage to uh to Newton?
>> Uh, I have not. Uh, I just kind of uh I
just kind of go with the flow to be
honest. So,
>> Gotcha. Hey, good luck to you.
>> Thank you. Thank you.
>> We have time for a few more. We'll go
with Cassidy Hill.
>> Yeah. I got so enthralled with your
Panther story earlier, we forgot to ask
about another one. Um, your dad had a
pretty interesting road to the NFL as
well.
>> And what kind of advice has he given
you? How much has he helped you prepare
for for this moment and and maybe kind
of getting to live out his dream as well
a little bit?
>> Uh, I wouldn't even say live out his
dream. I feel like he he had his dream.
He went to live he played a couple
years. So, I'll say it's definitely his
dream to see me in the NFL. Uh, but I've
been getting NFL training since I've
been a little boy. Uh, since I I grew up
playing football. He was in the NFL when
I was born. So, I mean, I just grew up
playing football. Uh, found found a love
for the game and football at a young
age. So, yeah.
>> Is there something that he was able to
teach you when you were young that that
really kind of helped you lock in and
you feel like it's helped you get to
this point?
>> Uh, just my work ethic. uh the little
thing like talent's cool but the work
ethic and what you do to be better than
the guys is what makes you great.
>> And then just one more for me. Have you
been to a Panthers game before?
>> Uh I have not been to the Panthers game.
The closest thing I've been to I played
uh what's the rivalry?
>> Uh Tennessee versus NC State. We played
at Bank of American
game was playing at the stadium.
>> Pretty cool. You'll your first one will
be you'll play in it.
>> Yeah, it's crazy.
>> Thank you.